复习练习 1-39：动词时态变化中保持代词重音。
Review exercise 139. Consistent pronoun stress and changing verb tenses. 1. It
erodes them. 2. It eroded them. 3. It's eroding them. 4. It'll erode them if it
keeps up. 5. It'd erode them if it kept up. 6. It'd have eroded them if it kept
up. 7. The one that's eroded them is quite old. 8. It's eroded them for eons. 9. It
had eroded them before the last ice age. 10. It'll have eroded them by the end of
the millennium. 11. It ought to have eroded them. 12. It should have eroded
them. 13. It shouldn't have eroded them. 14. It should have eroded them. 15. It
shouldn't have eroded them. It could have eroded them. 17, it couldn't have eroded
them. 18, it could have eroded them. 19, it couldn't have eroded them. 20, it might
have eroded them. 21, it might have eroded them. 22, it must have eroded them. 23, it
must have eroded them. 24, it can have eroded them. 25. It can erodum.